Contact methods

Bulgaria 088 766 1154 (Mobile) vadimjobhg86@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/vadymkuznetsov-60605193 (LinkedIn) vadim-job-hg.github.io/ (Portfolio)

Skills

Laravel

Php

Teamwork

Languages

Russian (Native or Bilingual) Ukranian (Native or Bilingual) English (Elementary)

Certifications

jQuery Tutorial course Try Git

T D:

Try Django

Git Real 2

Try Python

Vadym Kuznetsov

PHP BACKEND DEVELOPER

Bulgaria

Overview

Professional Web Developer with more than ten years of experience in areas such as the Internet of Things, sales, educational courses, etc. Worked on integrating third-party software systems, such as payment systems, ERP, edge computing software for IoT applications. Developed APIs for mobile and pwa applications.

Experience

Kita Koch

PHP BACKEND DEVELOPER

July 2024 - Present (1 year 3 months)

Development of new functionality, bug fixing, microservices development, support.

Daxx Software Development Teams in Ukraine Full-stack Developer August 2017 - May 2024 (6 years 10 months)

Kharkiv

Full-stack Developer for many projects for Naava Green Walls. Was involved in the

development of monitoring systems for the condition of green walls and the development

of tools for remote control of watering schedules, lighting and air circulation. Engaged in API development for https://naava.app/

KnubiSoft

Full Stack Developer March 2016 - July 2017 (1 year 5 months) Kharkiv

Developed various applications from scratch.

Developed subsidiary applications for the Swedish department of the BCA. Gained development experience using the Phalcon framework

iDeus

Full Stack Developer

October 2014 - March 2016 (1 year 6 months)

Kharkiv

Was on the team developing the TesTeachers educational platform, which provides

insurance courses for US students.

Was involved in the implementation of the payment system, code refactoring and searching

for vulnerabilities in the system.

MobilLuck

Full Stack Developer

May 2013 - October 2014 (1 year 6 months)

Kharkiv

Worked as part of a team on the site https://www.mobilluck.com.ua/

Was developing tools for sales managers that helped them carry out mass revaluation of

items in an online store.

Developed a system for monitoring the items market and revaluation based on the

profitability and prices of goods from competitors.

Enrial

Full Stack Developer January 2013 - May 2013 (5 months)

Website development

Zorat Wheels

IT Support Specialist

August 2012 - December 2012 (5 months)

Developed a business card website for selling car components.

Education

KPI

Bachelor, Computer Science · (2006 - 2012)

KPCC

Programming for Computer technology and automated systems · (2003 - 2006)